Finding Aid for the Collection of Pamphlet Maps LSC.0990
UCLA Library Special Collections
- [Card files]
  - Ireland and its railways. London, George Philip & son, [1866?]; Col.map; 1. Ireland - Maps (Box 12)
  - Brazil, from official and other sources. Prepared in the International bureau of the American republics. [Washington? D.C.], 1905.; map. 95x93cm. fold. To 25x20cm.; 1. Brazil - Describtion and travel - Maps. (Box 24)
    Scale: 75 miles to 1 inch.
    Inset: Is. Das Rocas, and I. de Fernando de Noroncha.
    In case.
  - Kinnear, John Macdonald
    See: Kinneir, John Macdonald,1782-1830.
  - General-karte von der Europäischen Türkei. Berlin, Dietrich Reimer, Ca.1876.; Col.map; 1. Turkey - Maps (Box 22)
  - Grahams new map of England. And Wales. with part of Scotland, showing the mail coach, turnpike & railroads, canals &c. London, [ca.1840?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps I. Title. (Box 17)
  - The southern countries of India from Madrass To cape Comorin. Surveyed by Col. Kelly, Capt. Wersebe, and others. London, Wm. Faden, 1788.; Col.map; 1. India - Maps (Box 1)
  - National map of the territory of the United States from the Mississippi River to the Pacific Ocean. Made by the authority of the Hon. O.H. Browning. Compiled from authorized explorations of Pacific rail road routes, public surveys, and otherreliable data. by W.J. Keeler. Washingron, D.C. J.F. Gedney, c1867.; map. (Box 28)
    For full information consult Numbered Coll. Card Catalog.
  - Nach dem endgültigen eisenbahn tracé Und im auftrag der St. Gotthard-direction. Winterthur, Wurster, Randegger & co., 1880.; Map.; 1. Switaerland - Maps (Box 22)
  - Kaempfer, Engelbert, 1651-1716.
    See the following entry in this catalog: [Buache, Philippe] 1700-1773. Carte desterres aux environs du Japon. [1753]
  - Juta's map of South Africa, from the Cape to the Zambesi. New and rev. ed. Cape Town, J.C. Juta & co., 1903.; Col.map.; 1.South Africa - Maps. (Box 10)
    London, Edward Stanford, 1903.
  - Julien, Roch-Joseph
    See the following entry in this cagalog: Etats de la maison de Brunswick-Luneburg, Et de leurs frontiers. Paris, Julien, 1758.
  - Letts's map of the Balkan peninsula and Turkey in Asia. London, [ca.1880]; Col.map.; 1. Balkin peninsula - Maps; 2. Turkey - Maps (Box 3)
  - Leigh, Samuel
    See the following entry in this catalog: Hall, Sidney - Leigh's new roadmap of England.
  - Topographical map of Lake Tahoe and surrounding country, by Ferdinand von Leicht, & J.D. Hoffmann. San Francisco, 1873.; col.map; 1. Tahoe, Lake - Maps; x Lake Tahoe (Box 31)
  - La carte dv Bovrdelois, dv pays de Medoc, et de la Prevosté de Born. Salmon Rogers sculp. Jean le Clerc excudit., 1657-1736.; 1. France - Maps. (Box 35)
  - A new map of the Kingdoms of Spain and Portugal with their principal divisions.London, Laurie & Whittle, 1808.; Col.map.; 1. Spain - Maps. 2. Portugal - Maps. (Box 24)
  - A plan of the county of Mid-Lothian, or Shire of Edinburgh. [London?], 1763.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 12)
  - A plan of Edinburgh and the country adjacent from an actual survey. Edinburgh, William Creech, 1786.; Map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 12)
  - Map of Virginia City and the Comstock lode, state of Nevada, showing the latest changes up to Jan. 1, 1875. n.p., steam print of F. Korbel & bros., col.map.; 1.Nevada-Maps. 2.Comstock lode, Nev. - Maps (Box 31)
  - Provincia do Rio de Janeiro. Rio de Janeiro, E. & H. Laemmert, 1866.; Col.map.; 1. Brazil - Maps. (Box 24)
  - McBride
    See the following entry in this catalog: Finley, S.H. - The official map of Orange county. 1924.
  - London and the country adjacent. London, J. Luffman, 1812.; col.map. (Box 17)
  - City map of Los Angeles. Los Angeles, 1913.; 1 map. 70 x 63cm.; No scale indicated. (Box 31)
    Showing locations of Los Angeles Investment Company acreage, built-up tracts, subdivisions, And vacant and improved business properties.
  - Lloyd's. map of. New York, J.T. Lloyd, 1861-1863.; 4 maps; 1. [Each area] - maps. (Box 30)
  - Lloyd's. map of. New York, J.T. Lloyd, 1861-1863.; maps. (Box 30)
    Lloyd's new map of the United states, the Canadas and New Brunswick., 1862; 1863.- Lloyd's official map of the state of Kentucky, 1863.- Lloyd's official map of the state of Virginia. revised to 1862, c1861.
  - Lloyd, H.H. & co.
    See the following entry in this catalog: New map of the United states. 1872
  - Perris' miners map of the desert region of Southern California embracing the counties of San Bernardino, Riverside and Orange, and portions of the adjacent counties, showing mining districts, forest reserves, Indian reservations, and county boundaries. Compiled and drawn in the office of the chief engineer of the Southern Pacific Railway.from data acquired by Fred T. Perris. Chicago, Rand, McNally, 1896.; 1 col. map. 61 x 87cm.; Scale: Eight miles to one inch. (Box 32)
  - Dépot général de la Guerre Sous la direction de Mr. le lt.ga. Pelet, et publiée en, 1832.; map.; 1. France - Maps. (Box 17)
  - France: tableau général des chemins de fer et des canaux, dressé par V. Levasseur, ingénieur. Paris, Maison Basset, [ca.1860?]; Map. (Box 24)
  - Map of the environs of London from the Ordance survey. London, Edward Stanford, [ca. 1890?]; Map.; 1. London - Maps. I. Stanford, Edward, publ. (Box 14)
  - Map of the county of London showing the Boundary of the jurisdiction of the London County Council. London, Edward Stanford, 1892.; Col.map; 1. London - Maps. I. Stanford, Edward, publ. (Box 14)
  - Map of the City of Los Angles and western Suburbs compiled for Chandler & Mall city Ciculators, of the Los Angles Herald. [Los Angles(?)], 1893.; 1. Los Angles (1893) - Maps (Box 32)
    Cover title: Pocket Map of Los Angles city.
  - Map of South Africa, Cape Colony, Natal, Etc. London, Edward Stanford, [ca. 1880?]; Col.map.; 1. South Africa - Maps; I. Stanford, Edward, publ. (Box 14)
  - Map of Kyushu. Nagasaki, Bunkindo, 1813.; 1. Japan - Maps. (Box 25)
  - Map of Canada east and west. New York, Horace Thayer & co., 1852.; col.map.; 1. Canada - Maps. I. Ensign's & Thayer, pub. (Box 31)
    c1848 by Ensign's & Thayer.
  - Map of all the railroads in the United States in operation and progress. New York, Henry V. Poor, [1854?]; 1. U.S. - Maps. 2. Railroads - U.S. - Maps.; I. Poor, Henry Varnum (Box 31)
  - Map of the county of the city of Glasgow, as divided into municipal wards. [Edinburgh] Bartholomew, 1912.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 22)
    Gift of Professor Roland D. Hussey.
  - McClelland, D.
  - Migliaria, Giambattista
    See the following entry in this catalog: Chiesa, Andrea - Carta topografico. del Bolognese. 1762.
  - Post charte der kaiserl. koenigl. erb-landen. [Vienna?], 1782.; Col.map.; 1.Western europe to Rumania. (Box 1)
  - Orbis terrae novissima descriptio. I.Hondius sculpt. I. le Clerc excis., 1602.; map.; 1. World maps, (Box 35)
    Ex libris Warern C. Shearman
  - Masters
    See the following entry in this catalog: Days, W. - County of Somerset. l800.
  - A new and accurate map of the county of Cornwall from an actual survey. London, William Faden, 1784.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 22)
  - Maps
    The map collections in the Department of Special Collections may be located in this catalog under author or country. For additional information please consult the shelf list, available at the public reference desk.
    Atlases can be located in the Printed Books catalog.
  - Map of the seat of war, in the northern part of Europe. London, John Stockdale, 1812.; 4 col.map sheets.; Map box title includes ". comprehending .the whole Russian empire." From Ogden collection.; 1. Europe - Maps. I. Stockdale, John, publ. (Box 10)
    From Ogden collection.
  - A map of the northern part of France, with the United Netherlands, and the course of the Rhine from Upper Alsce to Dusseldorf. London, W. Faden, 1815.; Col.map.; 1. Europe - Maps. I. Faden, William, publ. (Box 22)
  - Map of the Meath & Ward hunting district. Dublin, Hodges, Smith & co., 1862.; Col.map.; 1. Ireland.- Maps. (Box 13)
  - Mortier, Cornelis, publisher
  - Carta general (en dos hojas) del archipiéago Filipino. Madrid, Direction de Hidrografia, 1875.; Col.map.; 1. Philippine Islands - Maps. (Box 24)
    HojacII. No. 60. Hoja I. no.59.
    Corregida en 1888.
    Issued by the War Department, Adjutant General's office. Military Information Division, 1899.
  - Mitchell's reference & distance map of the United States, by J.H. Young. Philadelphia, S.A. Mitchell, 1834, c1833.; map. 54½x70 in. fold. to 12x9½ in.; Scales: 25mi. to the inch.; 1.U.S. Maps. I. Young, James Hamilton. (Box 28)
    In portfolio with title Mitchell's map of the United States.
    "Engraved by J.H. Young, F. Dankworth, E. Yeager & E.F. Woodward."
    "On this map will be found every county, township, parish, hundred, etc. in the United States arranged in conformity with the consus of 1830."
    Includes inset maps of cities, etc.
  - Mitchell's compendium of the internal improvements of the United States; comprising general notices of all the most important canals and rail-roads. with a brief notice of internal improvement in Canada and Nova Scotia. Philadelphia, Mitchell & Hinman, 1835.; 4. [V]-viii, 9-84p. incl. tables. Fold. map. 16sm. (Box 27)
  - Collection of maps. Philadelphia, S.A. Mitchell, 1831-1852; 9 maps (Box 27)
    The tourist's pocket map of the state of Georgia, 1836.- Map of the states of Louisiana, Mississippi & Alabama, l835.- The tourist's pocket map of the state of Tennesee, 1851.-The tourist's pocket map of the state of Virginia, 1845; 1849;, 1850; 1852.-
    Map of North America, 1831.- A route-book adapted to Mitchell's national map of the American republic, 1846.-
    1. [Each state mentioned] - Maps. I. Young James Hamilton
  - Bell Collection. The Strait of Anian. [Minneapolis], 1956.; 13 p. fac.map. (Box 22)
    Colored facsimile map describes Bering's route, 1725-30.
    I. Bering, Vitus Jonassen, 1681-1741.
  - Bell Collection. Antilia and America; a description of the l424 nautical chart and the Waldseemuller globe map of 1507. Minneapolis, 1955.; 10 p. illus; fac.map.; I.Waldseemiller, Martin, 1470-1518. xAntilia 1. West Indies - Maps. (Box 22)
    Colored facsimile of mss. map, the 1424 nautical chart.
  - New road map of Scotland, with all the lines of railway, canals, &c.&c., [ca. 1860?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 17)
  - A new map of South America, shewing it's general divisions, chief & towns; rivers, mountains &c., map.; 1. South America - Maps. (Box 35)
  - A new map of Central America shewing the different lines of Atlantic & Pacific communication. New York, 1854.; Col. map.; 1. Central America - Maps. I. Disturnell, John publ. (Box 22)
    Inset: Map of the Isthmus of tehuantepec reduced from the Original made by order of Dr. José de Garay.
  - A new and accvrat map of the world. Drawne according to ye truest descriptions latest discoueries & best obseruations yt haue beene made by English or strangers., [ca. 1600?]; map.; 1. World maps (Box 35)
  - Souveraineté de Dombe., 1695.; map.; 1. France - Maps. (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - The angler's map of the River Thames from Richmond to Henley. London, J. Netherclift, [ca.1880?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. 2. London - Maps (Box 17)
  - Kart over det sydlige Norge [Christiania] J.W. Cappellen, 1845.; Col.map.; 1. Norway - Maps (Box 12)
  - An accurate map of North and South Carolina with their Indian frontiers by Henry Mouzon and others. London, Sayer and Bennett, 1775.; Col.map.; 1. North Carolina - Maps. 2. South Carolina - Maps. (Box 28)
    One panel with inset missing.
  - Mountaine, William
    See the following entry in this catalog: Halley, Edmund, 1656-1742. A correct chart of the terraqueous globe London, 1794.
  - Le nouvean guide de l'etranger dans les 20 arrondissements de Paris. Paris, 1888.; Col.map. with city guide.; 1. Paris - Maps (Box 24)
  - Le nouveau guide de l'etranger dans les 20 arrondissement de Paris. Paris, Logerot, 1867; Col.map.; 1. Paris - Maps (Box 24)
  - 20 arrondissements de Paris. Paris, Logerot, 1865.; Col.map.; 1. Paris - Maps (Box 24)
  - Nouvaux mappemonde ou globe terrestre avec des tables et des remarqes pour conduire a la connoissance de la geographic et de LShistoire., map.; 1. World maps (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Map of the city of Memphis and suburbs. Memphis, Tenn., Donoho & Bukley, n.d., Col.map; 1. Memphis - Maps (Box 25)
  - Map of eastern Virginia, comp. from the best authorities. Washington, D.C., W.H. & O.H. Morrison, 1864.; col.map; 1. Virginia - Maps. I. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey. (Box 31)
    Comp. and printed at the Coast Survey Office.
  - Railroad map of the state of New Mexico. Santa Fe, N.M., 1913.; col.map.; 1. Railroads - Mew Mexico - Maps. (Box 8)
  - N.H., J.B. Rand, 1872.; Col.map.; l.U.S. - Maps. I. Lloyd, H-H. & Co II. Rand, J B (Box 31)
    1872 publication date label pasted over 1867.
  - A large draught of Bombay-Harbour on the coast of Mallabar in the East Indies. London, Win. Rerbert, 1763.; Map.; 1. India - Maps (Box 3)
  - A Panoramic view of the entrenched position of the allied armies of England & Francebefore Sebastopol. London, Stannard & Dixon, 1855.; Col.map.; 1. Russia - Maps (Box 18)
  - A new map of Palestine and the adjacent countries. London, Thomas Varty, ca.1840.; Col.map.; 1. Palestine - maps. (Box 15)
  - [London?] Bacon's Geographical Establishment, [ca.1850?]; Col.map. (Box 13)
  - Pacific crest trailway atlas. [Pasadena, 1945]; 1. The West - Maps (Box 22)
    notebook with maps
  - Ordnance Survey Office, Southampton
    See: Gt. Brit. Ordnance survey.
  - Oliver & Boyd's new travelling map of England & Wales. [Edinburgh, ca.l83O?]; col.map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 17)
  - The oarsman's and angler's map of the river Thames, from its source to London Bridge. London, James Reynolds & Sons, 1881.; Col.map.; 1. London - Maps (Box 17)
  - Nouvelle carte pour servir a l'histoire de l'empire d'orient depuis les premiers empereurs remains., 1. Europe, Easter, - Maps. (Folder 37)
  - Nouveau plan des environs de Paris. Paris, Bernardin-Béchet & fils, [1850?]; Col.map.; 1. Paris - Maps (Box 24)
  - Pianta topografica della sitta di Roma dell'anno 1849. Roma, Niccola de Antoni, Map.; 1. Rome -Maps (Box 13)
    Very simila to Canina, L:Pianta topografica
  - Pianta della citta di Roma con la indiczione di tvtte le antichita e nvovi abbellimenti. Rome, Venanzio Monaldini, 1827.; Map.; 1.Rome - Maps (Box 13)
  - Pianta del granducato di Toscanadi S.M.I. n.p., n.d., mss. col.map.; 1.Italy - Maps. 2. Maps, manuscript (Box 8)
  - Phelps & Watson's historical and military map of the border & southern states. New York, Gaylord Watson, 1867, c.1862; 36 p. col.map; 1. Southern states-maps. 2. U.S. - Civil war - maps. I. Watson, Gaylord (Box 31)
  - Tabvla itineraria ex illustri Peutingerorum bibliotheca quae Augusta Vindelicorum beneficio Marci Velseri, septem-viri augustani. In lucem edita., Map in 8 sheets.; 1. Maps, Early. 2. Geography, Ancient - Maps. I. Welser, Marcus, 1558 - 1614. xVelseri, (Box 35)
  - A new and complete railroad map of the United States. New York, presented by the Home Insurance Company of New York, [1858]; Col.map; 1. U.S. - Maps. 2. Railroads - U.S. - Maps. (Box 31)
    Covers area generally east of Mississipoi river.
  - Perrine's new topographical war map of the southern states, with a chronology of the great revbellio. V.p., v.d., l. Southern states -maps. 2. U.S. Civil war - maps. (Box 31)
    3 vols.
    cop.1: Indiananpolis, C.O. Perrine & co, 1863.
    cop. 2:Baltimore, Henry Taylor [1863?]
    cop.3:San Franciso, H.H. Bancrift & co., [1865?]
    cop.2&3 include: A concise history of the war. Designed to accompany Perrine's new war map of the southern states, with an introduction and statistical appendix, compiled from authentic sources, by. Lt.-col. John S. Bishop.
    cop.2: 132, i-xipp.
    cop. 3: 213, i-vi p.
  - Paris et ses monuments; nouveau guide pour visiter toutes les curiosité de Paris. Paris, Martinet, [1866?]; Col.map. (Box 24)
  - Plan de Paris. Paris, Pierotti, [ca.1860?]; Col.map; 1.Paris - Maps (Box 24)
  - Plan de Paris en 1866 divisé en 20 arrondissements. Paris, A. Bes et F. Dubreuil, Col.map.; 1. Paris - Maps (Box 24)
  - Poor, Henry Varnum, 1812-1905.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Map of all the railroads in the United States in operation and progress [1854?]
  - Post route map of the states of Kentucky and Tennessee. N.p., n.d., Col.map.; 1.Kentucky - Maps; 2. Tennesee - Maps. (Box 26)
    "Lower part:
    cover-title.
    Engraved by D. McClelland, Wash. D.G.
  - Post route map of the states of Virginia and West Virginia. n.p., n.d., col.map.; 1. Virginia - Maps. 2. West Virginia - Maps. (Box 26)
    "Lower part"
    Engraved by D. McClelland, Wash., D.C.
  - Príncipe de la Paz
    See: Godoy Alvarez de Earia Ríos Sánchez y Zarzosa, Manuel, principe de la Paz, 1767-1851.
  - Progressive map service. Map of county, California. Fresno, Progressive map service, ca.1916.; 9 maps.; 1. [Each county] - Maps. I. Chamberlin, Daniel W. II. Vincenz, (Box 30)
    "Data obtained from government and private sources, complied, published, and copyrighted by Progressive Map Service, Dan. W. Chamberlin."
    Calaveras, n.d. - Fresno, n.d. - Kern, n.d.-Madera, c1916.-Marin, n.d.-Marin, n.d.-Mariposa, c1916.-
    Mono, n.d. - Santa Barbara, n.d.- Ventura, n.d.
  - Punnett brothers
    See the following entry in this catalog: Weber (C.F.) and company, pub. Weber's map of county, California 1914.
  - Official Auto Road Map of Maine, New Hampshire and Vermont. Chicago and New York., 1927. (Box 32)
  - Indexed pocket map. Tourists' and shippers' guide. v.p. v.d. (Box 32)
    The library has the following guides:
    Canada: British Columbia, Alberta, Ontario and Saskatchewan.
    Mexico: Mexico, Sinaloa, Durango and Sonora.
    United States: Washigton.
  - Collection of maps. Chicago, Rand, McNally & co., 1878-1925; Map of Mexico, c.1914.; 1.[Each area] - Maps.; 25 maps (Box 30)
    Coahuila, México, indexed pocket map, c1925.-Standard map of City and County of San Francisco, n.d.-Map of Centrakl America, Indexed county and township map of Alabama, c1882.-Alabama, c1892.-Arkansas, c1911.-Arkansas, c1906.-Indexed county and township pocket map California, c1912.-Indexed maps of California and Nevada, c1878.-
    County map of California, c1887.-Standard map of California and Nevada, 1888 (2 cops.).- Indexed county map of Kentucky, c1882.-Indexed county and township map Louisiana, c1883; c1892; c1894.-Indexed county and township Mississippi. C1894.-Indexed map of New York, c1881. - Indexed county and railroad Tennessee, c1894.-Indexed county and township pocket map Utah, c1906.- Indexed railroad and county Virginia, c1886.- Indexed county and railroad West Virginia, c1910; Indexed county and railroad pocket map c1892.- Indexed map of the province of New Brunswick 1877.- Map of the West Indies, 1892 (Indexed Atlas of the World). Standard map of the world, n.d.
  - Rand, J.B.
    See the following entry in this catalog: New map of the United States 1872.
  - Railway station map of London and its environs. London, W.H. Smith & son, n.d., Col.map.; 1.London - Maps (Box 13)
  - Map of Minneapolis, being a subdivision of parts of the "Chadwick" and " Lindely Frederick and Mckibbin" Tract of the Rancho san Refael, Los Angeles County, California. Los Angeles, Los Angeles Lithographic, Co. [1887?]; ?G4364 L875G5 1887; Col. map. 57 x 93cm.; Scale 1:1, 800 approx.
    Surveyed in October 1887 by King and Winston.
  - Carte de la partie septentrionale de l'empire Otoman. [Paris?], 1774.; Col.map.; 1. Euope, Eastern - Maps. 2. Turkey - Maps (Box 3)
  - Rittenhouse, Jack DeVere, 1912-
    See the following entry in this catalog: Disturnell's treaty map; the map that was part of the Guadalupe Hidalgo treaty ...
  - A map of the provinces of Delhi, Agrah, Oude, and Allahabad, comprehending the countries lying between Delhi, and the Bengal-Provinces. London, Andrew Dury, 1777.; Col. map.; 1.India - Maps (Box 3)
  - A map of Bengal, Bahar, Oude & Allahabad, with part of Agra and Delhi, exhibiting the course of the Ganges from Hurdwar to the sea. London, Wm. Faden, 1786.; Col. map.; 1. India - Maps (Box 2)
  - Hindoostan. [London?] J. Rennell, 1782.; Col. map.; 1.India - Maps (Box 1)
  - Rand McNally & Co's sectional map of Kansas., 1900. (Box 32)
  - Rand, McNally & co.'s indexed county and township map of Arizona, with a new and original compilation and index designating all post office towns and railroad stations Also, an alphabetically arranged list of all railroads in the territory also, of the counties, lakes, rivers, etc., etc. Chicago, Rand McNally & co., [c1881]; 14 p. fold. map. 17cm.; 1. Arizona - Maps. (Box 30)
  - Official Auto Road Map of the New York. Chicago and New York., 1926 and 1927. (Box 32)
  - Official Auto Road Map of Massachusetts, Connecticutt and Rhode Island. Chicago and New York., 1927. (Box 32)
  - Theatre de la guerre du Rhin et de Westphalie, ou seconde carte pariculiere de l'atlas topographique et militaire de la guerre d'allemagne. Paris, Julien, 1760.; Col. map.; 1.Germany - Maps. (Box 8)
  - Roadmap of Switzerland. en partie tirée de l'atlas topographique. Zurich, H.F. Leuthold, 1867.; Col.map.; 1. Switzerland - Maps. (Box 12)
  - Actual survey of the county of Salop [ Shropshire] London, Rocque, 1752.; Col. map; xRocque, John 1.Gt. Bhit. - Maps (Box 16)
  - A topographical map, of the county of Berks London, J. Rocque, 1761.; 2 col.map sheets.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 16)
  - A topographical map of the county of Surrey. completed and engraved by Peter Andrews. London, M.A. Rocque, [1765]; 2 Col.map sheets; I. Rocque, Mary Ann 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps; II. Andrews, Peter (Box 16)
  - Rocque, John
    See: Rocque, Jean, d. 1762.
  - Rocque, Mary Ann, publisher.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Rocque, Jean, 1704?-1762. A topographical map of the county of Surrey [1765]
  - Romano, Giacomo Filippo Ameti
    See: Ameti, Giacomo Filippo
  - Carte generale des monts Pyrenees, et parte des royaumes de France et d'Espagne. [Paris?, 1780?]; Map. (2 sheets); 1. France - Maps. 2. Spain - Maps (Box 4)
  - Royer, Edgar
    See the following entry in this catalog: Seattle pioneer pocket guide. Seattle...
  - Sedes belli, of the stoel des oorlogs in den landen, van Braband, Gelderelandtz, Kleef, en Luykerland. Ambsterdam, Iohannes Covens en Cornelis Mortier, [ca.1750?]; 2 map sheets. (Box 4)
    I. Covens, Johannes.
    II. Mortier, Cornelis.
    1. Netherlands - Maps.
  - Seattle pioneer pocket guide. Seattle, 18 -19., 2 vols. (Box 32)
    v.24, no.7, July 1914
    v.29, no.4, April 1919
    I. Royer, Edgar.
  - An outline geological map of Tennessee, including portions of Mississippi, Alabama and Georgia. Cincinnati, E. Mendenhall, 1866; col.map (Box 31)
    1. Tennessee - Maps.
  - Sayer, Robert, 1725-1794, publisher.
    See the following entry in this catalog: The catholic Netherlands ... London, 1772.
  - Sanson d'Abbeville
    See:
    Sanson, Nicolas, 1600-1667.
    Sanson, Nicolas, 1626-1648.
    Sanson, Guillaume, -1703.
    Sanson, Adrien, -1708.
    Sanson, Pierre Moulard.
  - Les etats de la couronne de Pologne, ou sont les royaume de Pologne, duches de Prusse, Mazovie, Russie Noire, &c. Duches de Lithuanie, Volhynie, Podolie, &c, de l'Ukraine. Par S le Sr. Sanson d'Abbeville... Paris, Robert de Vaugondy, 1769; Col.map (Box 2)
    1. Germany - Maps.
    2. Russia - Maps.
    xSanson d'Abbeville
  - Slovansky zemevid. Praze, 1842; Col.map. (Box 24)
    1. Europe, Eastern - Maps.
  - ...Geografia del territorio Bolognese... [Bologna?], [1750?]; Map. (Box 4)
    1. Italy - Maps.
  - Afrique. Dessin#x00E9; par J. Hansen. Paris. Maison Andriveau-Goujon-H. Barrère, 1895; Col.map. (Box 10)
    1. Africa - Maps